BMT Diagnostics is an Israeli company focusing onÂ bringing innovative productsÂ andÂ developing customer-friendly rapid diagnostic tests.BMT has developedÂ and pioneeredÂ a first of its kind Lab-On-Timeâ„¢ worldwideÂ patented platformÂ of No-Step integratedÂ Rapid-Diagnostic-TestÂ devices that includes: Strep A, Influenza A+B, RSV, COVID19 Ag tests and more.TheÂ platform reducesÂ test performance complexity, making it simpler and more intuitiveÂ for the end-user.Â ThisÂ improvesÂ the process of patient screening,Â shiftingÂ patientÂ testingÂ from centralized labs to point-of-careÂ and self-use,Â thereby improving healthcare provision.We are seekingÂ â€“Â importers andÂ distributors in major territories for our product portfolio.
